

Sports-focused field and post-production assistant with a background in reality television, outdoor adventure, and professional football. Holds a bachelor's in film from one of the top-ranking schools in both film and academics. Boasts diverse experience, including projects with two major TV networks, HBO, and Netflix.

Professional Experience

NFL Seasonal Production Assistant

N FL, Culver City, CA October 2019 - Present

- Develop and deliver all motion and still graphics for shows
- Generate headshots and action shot cutouts
- Serve as quality control for all elements prior to final delivery
- Ensure a factual display of player and team information

NFL Documentary Production Assistant

"Hard Knocks," HBO, Oakland, CA July 2019 - August 2019

- Traveled with the crew and NFL team for joint practices and preseason games
- Logged and assisted in selecting footage
- Assisted in managing online content for the show
- Set up shot visualsand helped prep players for individual interviews

Set Production Assistant

"American Ninja Warrior". Los Angeles, CA August 2018 -June 2019

- Stayed positive, alert, and ready to respond to requests for help at any time, despite shooting overnight
- Directed competitors to correct locations at the proper time
- ♦ Assisted in obstacle course setup and tear down
- Aided in training on location PAs
- Traveled with the crew to competition sites around the country

Junior Production Assistant

Ultimate Beastmaster(Netflix), Santa Clarita, CA February 2018 - July 2018

- Completed frequent runs for producers and directors
- ♦ Transported audio and filming equipment
- ♦ M ad e sc hedu les, logs, and shot I i st for post- product io n team
- ♦ Ensured meals were ordered and on time during each day of production

123 Your Street, Austin, TX 72345 haze I rei d@exa m p le.com (123)456-7890

Education

Rhode Island School of Design Providence, RI, May 2017

Key Skills

- Interpersonal communication
- Proofreading
- Audio board operation
- ♦ Studio cameras
- Video editing
- Set up and strike